let easyadditionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 8 + 19",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 7",
        AnswerA: "28",
        AnswerB: "29",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 10",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "21",
        AnswerC: "22",
        AnswerD: "23",
        correctAnswer: "23",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 3",
        AnswerA: "39",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "41",
        AnswerD: "42",
        correctAnswer: "41",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 + 6",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "47",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 + 22",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 11 + 17",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 8",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "33",
        AnswerC: "34",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "34",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 + 19",
        AnswerA: "27",
        AnswerB: "28",
        AnswerC: "29",
        AnswerD: "30",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 + 17",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "43",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "45",
        correctAnswer: "42",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 + 17",
        AnswerA: "34",
        AnswerB: "35",
        AnswerC: "36",
        AnswerD: "37",
        correctAnswer: "34",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 + 15",
        AnswerA: "29",
        AnswerB: "30",
        AnswerC: "31",
        AnswerD: "32",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 16 + 16",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 + 18",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 + 19",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 20 + 20",
        AnswerA: "39",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 21 + 21",
        AnswerA: "40",
        AnswerB: "42",
        AnswerC: "44",
        AnswerD: "46",
        correctAnswer: "42",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 22 + 22",
        AnswerA: "44",
        AnswerB: "45",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "47",
        correctAnswer: "44",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 23",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "46",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 + 24",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "48",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 + 25",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "50",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 6",
        AnswerA: "27",
        AnswerB: "28",
        AnswerC: "29",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 + 18",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "33",
        AnswerC: "34",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "35",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 + 8",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 + 7",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 27",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 + 23",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "27",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 19 + 13",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 6 + 7",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "14",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 + 8",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 5 + 39",
        AnswerA: "43",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "46",
        correctAnswer: "44",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 + 9",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
]